ROBERT FLAHERTY

Looking to get back into the field I chose...

Arlington, WA 98223 mr.flaherty@gmail.com 360-926-3400

#readytowork After moving to Arlington finding employment in the Information Technology field was challenging. Over the last ten years I've taken jobs from volunteering at the Bonney Lake Food Bank and eventually driving for them to various areas of the county to pick up donations, to getting my grade 8 soccer referee certificate and volunteering to referee the SnoCo soccer league. I spent three years working for Tractor Supply Co. as a Receiving Manager, and really enjoyed that because inventory satisfied and stimulated my computer studies. A short stint with Amazon running their dock using forklift and aerial lifts, but Covid-19 has been an impact to myself, as well as so many others, and I am desperate to get back into a work routine. Thank you.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Certified Team Leader / Certified Trainer I

APAC Customer Services, INC

June 2009 to June 2010

Manage and develop agents on my team, while supporting prepaid call floor, and operations managers in administrative responsibilities. Lead efficient and effective operations, to meet Key Performance Indicators for revenue growth. Recently certified in the current stage of modern methodology training; Coaching to Customer Experience, Customer Service Soft Skills, and the T3 Training Certificate introducing Gifted Roles, IEDDDT, and more

Program Ready Trainer

Convergys Corporation

May 2008 to May 2009

Establish clear foundations and expectations in terms of ethics, integrity, corporate social responsibility, and all the other converging concepts in this area that are the bedrock of all good modern responsible organizations. Recognized and promoted for top seller August 2008, most notable of several achievements; call quality, excellent client satisfaction, and perfect attendance.

Database Administrator

Pelstar, Inc

December 2007 to April 2008

Lead the Kaizen event that introduced methods with the SQL database that reduced downtime and site administration resulting in increased revenue and decreased department expenditures while performing freelance/ contractual assignments for the company.

Platform Specialist

Convergys Corporation

September 2001 to March 2002

Providing support and assisting in the development of project members, while resolving escalated issues, supervisor requests, and coaching for agents on the floor. Providing cross-system support and solutions for customers, as well as business's for the more complex networking conflicts.

Team Chief

Air Defense Artillery

March 1991 to September 2000

Recognized Team Chief receiving several awards and achievements, my first leadership role was as Distinguished Honor Graduate in Air Defense Artillery and speaking about teamwork and success for the graduating class Ft. Bliss, Tx. 1992.

EDUCATION

High school diploma

White River High School - Buckley, WA September 1988 to June 1992

SKILLS

- Databases
- .NET Framework
- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Microsoft Outlook
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Microsoft Word
- Macromedia Dreamweaver
- Network
- Network Administration
- Network Protocols
- Data Analysis Skills
- TCP/IP
- Active Directory
- Operating Systems

- System AdministrationTCP
- LAN
- Technical Support
- Network Support
- Microsoft Windows Server
- Microsoft Windows
- DNS
- DHCP
- Database Administration

MILITARY SERVICE

Branch: army Rank: specialist September 1992 to September 2000

Commendations:

air defense artillery 16s

good conduct aa national desert storm

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP) Present

A+ Certified

Present

Network+

Present

Microsoft Office Specialist

Present